What's one of the skills you had to learn or a way you had to change in order to support your company as a group?
Well, I'll just start at the beginning.
I had to be willing to have people who disagreed with my choice, including my colleagues, my friends and my family.
And so most people cannot get past one, two or three of those.
And so they just stay stuck.
So, I mean, the first thing you have to do is be willing to be disagreed with.
And I think you also need to be willing to look cringe
because you will be cringe because you've never done it before.
And so it is a prerequisite of doing something new that you will suck.
And so many people are afraid of sucking.
And as a result, they continue to lose because they never try.
Losers stay losers because they are afraid of losing.
So they never try.